var geographydata = {
  "total_size": 10,
  "questions": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "question":
          "On the basis of the status of development, resources can be classified as?",
      "option1": "Potential",
      "option2": "Developed stokes",
      "option3": "Reserves",
      "option4": "All of the above",
      "ans": "d",
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "question":
          "______ are the resources which are surveyed, and their quality and quantity have been determined for utilisation.",
      "option1": "Developed resources",
      "option2": "Reserves",
      "option3": "Stock",
      "option4": "Abiotic",
      "ans": "a",
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "question":
          "About _________ of India’s land area is plain, which provides facilities for agriculture and industry.",
      "option1": "44%",
      "option2": "35%",
      "option3": "45%",
      "option4": "33%",
      "ans": "a",
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "question":
          "__________ account for 30% of the total surface area of India.",
      "option1": "Deserts",
      "option2": "Mountains",
      "option3": "Plains",
      "option4": "Plateaus",
      "ans": "c",
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "question": "Chomolungma is located in which country?",
      "option1": "India",
      "option2": "Nepal",
      "option3": "Bhutan",
      "option4": "Tibet",
      "ans": "b",
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "question": "Which among the following is the world’s highest island?",
      "option1": "Hawii",
      "option2": "Borneo",
      "option3": "New Guinea",
      "option4": "Sumatra",
      "ans": "c",
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "question": "Ninety Mile Beach is located in which country?",
      "option1": "Australia",
      "option2": "United states",
      "option3": "Brazil",
      "option4": "Bangladesh",
      "ans": "a",
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "question": "Which of the following is the hottest star colour?",
      "option1": "Red",
      "option2": "Yellow",
      "option3": "Orange",
      "option4": "Blue",
      "ans": "d",
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "question":
          "Which among the following is not a part of the Mesozoic Era?",
      "option1": "Jurassic",
      "option2": "Triassic",
      "option3": "Cretaceous",
      "option4": "Carboniferous",
      "ans": "d",
    },
    {
      "id": 10,
      "question": "Which of the following is the smallest gulf in the world?",
      "option1": "Gulf of Aqaba",
      "option2": "Gulf of Guinea",
      "option3": "Gulf of California",
      "option4": "Gulf of Oman",
      "ans": "c",
    },
  ]
};
